不错！  搞定！
Alright, you're done.
我们来看一眼我的解决方法
Let's take a look at my solution.
第一步  我们创建一个整型常量作为loader ID
For our first step, we created a loader ID integer constant.
在activity里使用的时候要保证这些常量是唯一的
These just have to be unique for every loader you're using in your activity.
然后我们按照CursorLoader的需求在ForecastFragment中
Then we had forecast fragment implement the loader manager loader
实现了LoaderManager.LoaderCallbacks  数据类型为Cursor
callbacks with type cursor, as required by CursorLoader.
我们这里加上了三个LoaderCallbacks的接口方法
We added our three loader callback functions.
对于onCreateLoader  我们将用于创建cursor的ContentProvider的请求
For on CreateLoader we move the ContentProvider query we had for
放进来  然后用它来初始化CursorLoader
creating the cursor, and use this to initialize the CursorLoader.
在onLoadFinish
In onLoadFinish,
我们将ForecastAdapter的cursor和新的cursor交换
we swap the cursor in our ForcastAdapter with our new loaded one.
在onLoaderReset  我们会释放之前所用的资源
In onLoader reset, we want to release any resources that we might be using.
就这样
And that's it.
运行一下  保证一切功能正常
Let's run this, and make sure it's all working correctly.
正如你看到的  屏幕上显示一些天气信息
And, as you can see, some fabulous weather.
虽然看上去和上一章节我们实现的效果完全一样  但是
This is actually using the loader, even though it looks exactly like the output
这里的确是用的是loader
from the last section that we completed.